What's going on everybody, Tyson Smith here, and Matthew and I are so excited
to announce
that we have decided to democratize the JV system within the community.
And what that means for you is previously, we really only have the option for
people
to JV with Matthew and I, however, we've realized that you guys are doing such
a good
job of getting buy boxes all across the country and we want to see more of our
students do
deals with each other, so here's what we've decided to set up.
Number one, you're still going to have the option to go ahead and JV with me
and Matthew.
The way to do that is to go here and submit deals the same way you have before.
The only change we're doing with this is now we're only taking properties that
are located
in one of our approved buy boxes.
So if you're a beginner, you're looking to get a deal or you're anybody who
wants to
do deals with Matthew and I, all you need to do is go on over to our approved
buy boxes
where we have listed off every single buy box that we have developers in and we
can move
deals very quickly and exactly the specifications, or the price range, lot size
requirements
and anything else you would need to know to be successful.
However, with that being said, we also want to open up you guys to be able to
share your
buy boxes.
So if you have a buy box of a developer, you're more than welcome to share it
in the community
using the share your buy boxes tab, okay?
So all you would do is go to the community and post a deal in this tab, share
your buy
boxes, okay?
The only way to do that is when you go to post, you just make sure that you
select the category
as share your buy boxes, all right?
Now when you're submitting your buy boxes, this is, you know, your buyers are
your buyers.
So you're not going to be actually submitting who your developer or who your
custom home
builder is, you're just going to submit exactly what it is they're looking for.
When you go ahead and submit your buy box, you're going to follow this template
.
So you're going to put the title as where, you know, the city and state where
your buy
boxes and then the actual target area.
So ideally you should have a photo with a boundary like we've have here.
However, if your developer is looking in a specific zip code or perhaps a
specific area,
like maybe you have a developer in Bellmead Nashville or Woodland Hills, Dallas
, you're
fine to put that there as well.
However, having a map with clear boundaries shown is much better.
Then you're going to have a price range, right?
The amount the developer is looking to pay as well as the lot size requirements
.
So minimum and maximum acceptable lot sizes.
Sometimes you won't have a maximum and that's fine.
Then you're going to want to include any sort of deal breakers.
So anything that would kill the deal, right?
Maybe the property zone of wash, flood zone and easement.
Maybe your buyer doesn't want anything on the water or only wants stuff on the
water.
Whatever it is, just go ahead and include it in the deal breakers.
Now, now other members of the community are going to be able to actually go
target properties
that meet your developer's criteria.
And once they get them under contract, you guys are welcome to JV together.
And special note here, you need to make sure you execute a JV agreement with
the other
member prior to setting out any assignment contracts to the buyer, okay?
The JV agreement template can be found here, where you can click open.
And this is a JV agreement that you guys can sign.
When you're doing this, you would put your company name, the other community
member's
company's name, the property here.
You can go ahead and set the splits, however you like.
Typically, we recommend doing 50/50 as that's the most fair.
And then you can just set up whatever the arbitration is in case there is any
sort of
dispute, which hopefully there wouldn't ever be.
Go ahead and put it in your state and then you guys can both sign, okay?
So that is the first way to go ahead and JV with other community members, right
?
You post your buy boxes and other students can go ahead and find deals for you.
Alternatively, you can just post your deals inside the community as well.
So what if you get a deal under contract?
You can go ahead and post it here and have other students go and try and help
you find
a buyer for your deal, right?
The way you do that is you post it new deal in city where the property is, the
contract
price, the lot size, close of escrow, and any other additional terms or info.
So for instance, if we had this deal, if we were looking for a buyer for it, we
wanted
your guys's help.
We could post it here.
As you can see the address of what we have under contract for, the size of it,
close of
escrow, and then any additional terms.
Now, again, if any members of the community have a buyer who may be interested
in your
deal, they can reach out to you to see about Jay being it.
But one thing I'm going to tell you guys right now, every single person, all
right?
You do not try and market somebody else's deal in the community unless they
have expressly
given you permission to do so.
So if you see a deal listed inside the community, right, and you have a buyer
for it, you need
to reach out to that other community member and say, "Hey, I have a buyer for
your deal.
Am I allowed to market it to them?"
Okay?
Deal without permission is illegal, so do not do that, okay?
And another note that I'm going to say is, "Look, a core value of Lux Blueprint
Community
is honesty and integrity.
We are honest with another.
We operate from an abundance mindset when it comes to these deals, poaching
anybody's
deals, contacting other members' lead, stealing information, or any similar
behavior towards
fellow students will not be tolerated, and will result in immediate termination
from the
group, okay?
If we have any sign of proof that you're engaging any sort of dishonest
behavior like
this, we are immediately going to terminate you, and I personally will never do
business
with you ever again, not to mention every single person in my network will
never do business
with you ever again, okay?
Do not try and mess somebody, you know, screw somebody over to make a quick
buck.
That is a quick way.
Like, I don't know what you believe in, but you're, you know, that is going to
end very
poorly for you.
However, back to a lighter note is, look, we get so many JV submissions.
We get so many buy boxes, and we want you guys to all be able to take advantage
of this
and be able to do deals with each other.
So this is how we're setting it up so you guys can move forward and start doing
deals
with each other.
So get in there, post your buy boxes, post your deals, and let's all go make a
bunch
of money together.
If you have any questions, go ahead and make a post in the community.